What is it that you do to
kind of maintain that healthy work-life environment?
So what I would say is that we interview so
many people, so you get to see why people are leaving
companies, what they're looking for. And I think
what's happened is companies for the last decade
could afford to treat people like numbers and
people would still work and they're paying them
enough. But what happens when times get turbulent is
people kind of start waking up. And I think
what happened is during COVID, it put everything on
pause and it kind of made people realize like,
why do I do what I do? Do I actually like
my job? Am I happy where I'm at? And all these tech
companies, they thought that having free food and
having all these different things were going to
get people to stay. But people at the end of
the day, they don't really care about stuff like that.
What they mainly care about is knowing that the
company cares for them as a person and they have
actual room to grow and develop and
their life and their trajectory is getting better.